Guide to the Paul Ehrlich Papers SC0223
Department of Special Collections and University Archives
- General Files and Correspondence, Series 1
  - NECC: National Energy Conservation Challenge (Box 40, Folder 26)
  - New Party and Western New Party (Box 40, Folder 27)
  - New York Zoological Society (Box 40, Folder 28)
  - Oceanic Institute (Box 40, Folder 29)
  - Office of Environmental Affairs (Box 40, Folder 30)
  - Optimum Population and Environment (Box 40, Folder 31)
  - Outward Bound: Colorado (Box 40, Folder 32)
  - Overview (Box 40, Folder 33)
  - Overseas Development Council (Lester R. Brown) (Box 40, Folder 34)
  - The Pathfinder Fund (Box 40, Folder 35)
  - Peace and Freedom Party (Box 40, Folder 36)
  - People's Lobby (Box 40, Folder 37)
  - Planetary Synergy League (Box 40, Folder 38)
  - Planned Parenthood - Chicago (Box 40, Folder 39)
  - Planned Parenthood - Other (Box 40, Folder 40)
  - IPPF: International Planned Parenthood Fed.: see Brian Johnson correspondence file (Box 40, Folder 41)
  - PHP: Japan (Box 40, Folder 42)
  - Population Association of America (Box 40, Folder 43)
  - Population Communication Center (see also Poindexter, D.) (Box 40, Folder 44)
  - The Population Council (Box 40, Folder 45)
  - Population Control Academy (India): see also Kutty, in general file (Box 40, Folder 46)
  - Population Crisis Committee (Box 40, Folder 47)
  - Population Planning Association (Population Services, Inc.) (Box 40, Folder 48)
  - Population Services International (Box 40, Folder 49)
  - Population Stabilization LTD. (Box 40, Folder 50)
  - Problem Pregnancy Information Center (Box 40, Folder 51)
  - "Prospective": Church of Tomorrow - Brussels, 1973. Second Vatican Council: Dossiers. (Box 40, Folder 52)
  - Pygmy Forest: California Institute of Man in Nature (Box 40, Folder 53)
  - Right to Life (Box 40, Folder 54)
  - Research Center in Economic Development and Cultural Change (Box 40, Folder 55)
  - Resources to the Future, Inc.: Joseph Fisher, Wash. DC (Box 40, Folder 56)
  - The Ripon Society (Box 40, Folder 57)
  - San Francisco Institute of Animal Behavior (Box 40, Folder 58)
  - San Jose Teachers Assn. 1974 (Box 40, Folder 59)
  - San Mateo County Planned Parenthood (Box 40, Folder 60)
  - Science Foundation for Physics (Sydney, Australia) (Box 40, Folder 61)
  - Science Foundation for Physics (Sydney, Australia) (Box 40, Folder 62)
  - Scientists' Institute for Public Info., 1981 (Box 40, Folder 63)
  - Second American Revolutionary Force (Box 40, Folder 64)
  - SESPA: Science for the People (Box 40, Folder 65)
  - SIDEC (Box 40, Folder 66)
  - SPEC: Society for Pollution and Environmental Control (Box 40, Folder 67)
  - SPARE: Assn. to Spare the Pt. Arena Environment (Box 40, Folder 68)
  - Student Amer. Medical Assn. (Box 40, Folder 69)
  - Survivor's Group: 1973 (Box 40, Folder 70)
  - SUWA-NO-SE Island (Organizations) (Box 40, Folder 71)
  - SWOPSI (Box 40, Folder 72)
  - Tynesice Environmental Concern (England) (Box 40, Folder 73)
  - UNILAB (Box 40, Folder 74)
  - United Nations Day-World Holiday (Box 40, Folder 75)
  - United Nations (Box 40, Folder 76)
  - The Victor-Bostrom Fund for the International Planned Parenthood Federation (Box 40, Folder 77)
  - Virginia Club Woman, Feb. 1971 (Box 40, Folder 78)
  - World Affairs Council (Box 40, Folder 79)
  - World Life Research Institute (Box 40, Folder 80)
  - World Neighbors (Box 40, Folder 81)
  - Ehrlich Correspondence: H-Z
    - Hutcheson, Evelyn (Box 40, Folder 82)
    - Humphrey, Hubert (Box 40, Folder 83)
    - Jameson, Dave (Box 40, Folder 84)
    - Lader, Lawrence: NARAL (Box 40, Folder 85)
    - Lavern, George (Box 40, Folder 86)
    - Law, Cecil (Box 40, Folder 87)
    - Lawrence, Donald (Box 40, Folder 88)
    - Lees, Lester (Box 40, Folder 89)
    - Legget, Robert F. (Box 40, Folder 90)
    - Libby, William (Box 40, Folder 91)
    - Lidicker, Jr., W. Z. (Box 40, Folder 92)
    - Linacre: see also MacQuarie University, Australia (Box 40, Folder 93)
    - Loraine, John A. (Box 40, Folder 94)
    - Los Angeles County Museum (Box 40, Folder 95)
    - Loucks, Orie (Box 40, Folder 96)
    - McHarg, Ian (Univ. of Pennsylvania) (Box 40, Folder 97)
    - MacNeil, C. Don (Box 40, Folder 98)
    - Mason, Larry (Box 40, Folder 99)
    - May, Robert (Box 40, Folder 100)
    - Miller, Lee (Box 40, Folder 101)
    - Moore, Hugh (Fund) (Box 40, Folder 102)
    - Morinaga (1973) (Box 40, Folder 103)
    - Moss, W. Wayne (Box 40, Folder 104)
    - Muskie, Senator (Box 40, Folder 105)
    - Nixon (Box 40, Folder 106)
    - Novitski, Ed (Box 40, Folder 107)
    - Nasher, Raymond (Box 40, Folder 108)
    - Nelson, Senator Gaylord (Box 40, Folder 109)
    - Nuorteva, Pekka (Box 40, Folder 110)
    - Odetics (Box 40, Folder 111)
    - Odum, Eugene (Box 40, Folder 112)
    - Ogilvie, Stewart: see Hugh Moore Fund (Box 40, Folder 113)
    - Ogburn, Charlton Jr. (Box 40, Folder 114)
    - Olaf, Palme (Sweden) (Box 40, Folder 115)
    - Pendleton-Zentner (Box 40, Folder 116)
    - Peterson, Dr. Everett (Box 40, Folder 117)
    - Philogene, B. (Canada) (Box 40, Folder 118)
    - Pielou, E. C. (Canada) (Box 40, Folder 119)
    - Pirone, Dominick (Box 40, Folder 120)
    - Platt, John (Box 40, Folder 121)
    - Porter, Eliot (Box 40, Folder 122)
    - Proctor, John (Box 40, Folder 123)
    - Prout, Tim (Box 40, Folder 124)
    - Randall, Darrell (Box 40, Folder 125)
    - Real, Herman G. (Box 40, Folder 126)
    - Regier, Henry (Box 40, Folder 127)
    - Rohlf, F. James (Box 40, Folder 128)
    - Salk, Jonas (Box 40, Folder 129)
    - Sax, Dr. Karl (Box 40, Folder 130)
    - Saxena, K. N. (Box 40, Folder 131)
    - Schaefer, John (Box 40, Folder 132)
    - Seavey, Steven Ray (Box 40, Folder 133)
    - Shick, Charles (Box 40, Folder 134)
    - Singer, Fred (Box 40, Folder 135)
    - Singer, Pat (Box 40, Folder 136)
    - Sivers, Elsa and Carl (Box 40, Folder 137)
    - Sneath, P. H. A. (Box 40, Folder 138)
    - Spight, Tom M. (Box 40, Folder 139)
    - Stannard, Lewis J. (Box 40, Folder 140)
    - Stubbe, Wilfred (Box 40, Folder 141)
    - Tillson, Thomas (Box 40, Folder 142)
    - Tydings, Joseph (Box 40, Folder 143)
    - Van Den Bosch, Robert (Box 40, Folder 144)
    - Vaughan, Christopher (Ballantine, London) (Box 40, Folder 145)
    - Vaughan, Christopher (Ballantine, London) (Box 40, Folder 146)
    - Voevodsky, John (Box 40, Folder 147)
    - Wagner, Robert (Box 40, Folder 148)
    - Waldie, Jerome - Werner, Llewellyn (Box 40, Folder 149)
    - Weaver, The Venerable John J: Archdeacon of Califonia (Box 40, Folder 150)
    - Weeden, Alan (Box 40, Folder 151)
    - Weeden, Frank (via Cosovich, Glover) (Box 40, Folder 152)
    - Weingart - Film Brier Producitons (Box 40, Folder 153)
    - Westmen, W. (Australia) (Box 40, Folder 154)
    - Whitehill, James: see ZPG (Box 40, Folder 155)
    - Widmer, Carl (Peru) (Box 40, Folder 156)
    - Wiens, John (Box 40, Folder 157)
    - Wirtz, Willard (Box 40, Folder 158)
    - Wourms, J. P. (Box 40, Folder 159)
    - York, Herbert (Box 40, Folder 160)
    - Young, Allen (butterflies) (Box 40, Folder 161)
    - Young, Jim (Box 40, Folder 162)
    - Young, Richard (Box 40)
  - Annual Reviews: PRE Editorial Committee (Box 42, Folder 1)
  - Arctic Institute of North America (Box 42, Folder 2)
  - American Society of Zoologists (Box 42, Folder 3)
  - Assoc. for Voluntary Sterilization (Box 42, Folder 4)
  - Center for Growth Alternatives: see Equilibrium Fund (Box 42, Folder 5)
  - Center for Study of Democratic Institutions - now Institute for Higher Studies (Box 42, Folder 6)
  - Common Cause (see also in "Organizations") (Box 42, Folder 7)
  - Consumer Alliance (see also in "Organizations") (Box 42, Folder 8)
  - The Conservation Society (Box 42, Folder 9)
  - Ecological Society of America (Box 42, Folder 10)
  - Ecological Society of America: Ecology Awareness Award (Box 42, Folder 11)
  - Entomological Society of America (Box 42, Folder 12)
  - Forum for Contemporary History (Box 42, Folder 13)
  - Intecol (Box 42, Folder 14)
  - Former Classmates/Acquaintances/Name Alikes (Box 43, Folder 1)
  - Royal Aero Club of New South Wales (Box 43, Folder 2)
  - AOPA (Box 43, Folder 3)
  - Jeppesen & Co. (Important Revisions) (Box 43, Folder 4)
  - Requests for Autographs (Box 43, Folder 5)
  - Hawaii, 1969-1971 (Box 43, Folder 6)
  - Hawaii, 1972 (Box 43, Folder 7)
  - Hawaii, Spring 1973 (Box 43, Folder 8)
  - Hawaii, Spring 1974 (Box 43, Folder 9)
  - Hawaii, 1975 (Box 43, Folder 10)
  - Hawaii, 1976 (Box 43, Folder 11)
  - Hawaii, 1978 (Box 43, Folder 12)
  - Hawaii, Spring 1979 (Box 43, Folder 13)
  - PRE Bib-jlb (Box 43, Folder 14)
  - Scientific Societies (Box 43)
  - AIBS Member-at-Large file: including minutes of meetings (Box 43, Folder 15)
  - American Museum of Natural History: see also Rindge, F. in correspondence file (Box 43, Folder 16)
  - American Society of Oceanography (Box 43, Folder 17)
  - American Assoc. of University Women (Box 44, Folder 1)
  - Abortion Initiative Movement (Box 44, Folder 2)
  - American Cetacean Society (Box 44, Folder 3)
  - American Council of Learned Societies (Box 44, Folder 4)
  - American Eugenics Party (Box 44, Folder 5)
  - American Society for Ecological Education (Box 44, Folder 6)
  - Aspen Institute: Walter Orr Roberts (Box 44, Folder 7)
  - Association for Voluntary Sterilization (see Negative Population Growth) (Box 44, Folder 8)
  - Asia Foundation (Box 44, Folder 9)
  - Businessmen for the Public Interest (Box 44, Folder 10)
  - Northern California Committee for Environmental Information (Box 44, Folder 11)
  - California Citizen Action Group, 1974 (Box 44, Folder 12)
  - California Committee to Legalize Abortion (Box 44, Folder 13)
  - California Friends of Robert Frost (Box 44, Folder 14)
  - California Interagency Council on Family Planning (Box 44, Folder 15)
  - California World Hunger Conference, Oct. 23, 1969 (Box 44, Folder 16)
  - The Cambridge Institute (Box 44, Folder 17)
  - California Institute of Man in Nature - Olmstead (see Pygmy Forest) (Box 44, Folder 18)
  - Campaign to Check the Population Explosion (Box 44, Folder 19)
  - Canal Authority of the State of Florida (Box 44, Folder 20)
  - Capricorn Conservation Council (was ZPG Australia) (Box 44, Folder 21)
  - Center for Population Research: National Institute of Child Health & Human Development (Box 44, Folder 22)
  - Center for Population Studies (Box 44, Folder 23)
  - Center for Family Planning Program Development (Box 44, Folder 24)
  - Center for Constructive Change (Box 44, Folder 25)
  - Berkeley Center for Human Interactions (Box 44, Folder 26)
  - Center for Optimum Environments (Bowers) (Box 44, Folder 27)
  - Center for the Study of Democratic Instit. (see "Organizations") (Box 44, Folder 28)
  - Children by Choice Assn. (Australia) (Box 44, Folder 29)
  - Citizens Committee for Environmental Control (Penn.) (Box 44, Folder 30)
  - Coalition for a National Population Policy (Tydings) (Box 44, Folder 31)
  - Comite Anitnucleaire de Paris (Box 44, Folder 32)
  - Commission on Population Growth and the American Future (Box 44, Folder 33)
  - Comm. for Nuclear Responsibility (Box 44, Folder 34)
  - President's Commission on Population Growth and the American Future (Box 44, Folder 35)
  - Comm for Relevant Science (Box 44, Folder 36)
  - Concern, Inc. (Wash. DC) (Box 44, Folder 37)
  - Conservation Foundation (Box 44, Folder 38)
  - Conference of Actuaries in Public Practice (Box 44, Folder 39)
  - Conference for a United World - Free World, 1973 (Box 44, Folder 40)
  - Conference on National Priorities (Box 44, Folder 41)
  - MS: First National Congress on Optimum Population and Environment (Box 44, Folder 42)
  - Consumer Alliance (Box 44, Folder 43)
  - Council on Economic Priorities (Box 44, Folder 44)
  - Couseau Society (See also trip file, 1976 & 1977) (Box 44, Folder 45)
  - Dai Dong - See Fellowship of Reconciliation (Box 44, Folder 46)
  - Action Committee on Environmental Quality (George Brown) (Box 44, Folder 47)
  - Earth and Society (Box 44, Folder 48)
  - Earth Day, 1971 (Box 44, Folder 49)
  - Earth Day/Environmental Action (Box 44, Folder 50)
  - Earth Institute (Box 44, Folder 51)
  - Ecology Corp of America - Ecolo-G (Box 44, Folder 52)
  - Ecology Forum (Box 44, Folder 53)
  - Ecolux: Specialists in Environmental Science (Box 44, Folder 54)
  - Econotech Systems (Box 44, Folder 55)
  - Energy Policy Project, 1974 (various publications) (Box 44, Folder 56)
  - Environmental Awareness Assoc. (Box 44, Folder 57)
  - Environmental Action (Box 44, Folder 58)
  - Environmental Defense Fund (Box 44, Folder 59)
  - Environmental Clearinghouse (Box 44, Folder 60)
  - Environmental Fund (see Blackelder, Justin in corr.) (Box 44, Folder 61)
  - Environmental Health Task Force (Box 44, Folder 62)
  - Environmental Information Center (Robert Burnap) (Box 44, Folder 63)
  - Environmental Protection Agency (Box 44, Folder 64)
  - Environmental Sciences Institute (Box 44, Folder 65)
  - Environmental Studies Institute (Box 44, Folder 66)
  - Environmental Teach-In, 1970 (Box 44, Folder 67)
  - European Broadcasting Union (Box 44, Folder 68)
  - European Information Center for Nature Conservation - Nature in Focus (Box 44, Folder 69)
  - Family Planning Federation of Canada (Box 44, Folder 70)
  - Family Planning Perspectives (Box 44, Folder 71)
  - Fellowships of Reconciliation (see also Dai Dong) (Box 44, Folder 72)
  - Federal Union (Box 44, Folder 73)
  - Freedom From Hunger Committee (Northern California) (Box 44, Folder 74)
  - Forum for Contemporary History (Box 44, Folder 75)
  - Forum International (Box 44, Folder 76)
  - Foundation for Education in Ecology (Box 44, Folder 77)
  - Freedom from Hunger Campaign Publications (Box 44, Folder 78)
  - Gottlieb Duttweiler Institute for Social and Economic Studies (Box 44, Folder 79)
  - President- US (Box 44, Folder 80)
  - Congress- General (Box 44, Folder 81)
  - Senate- General (Box 44, Folder 82)
  - Calif. State Legislature (Box 44, Folder 83)
  - Arizona Governor - 1971 hassle (Box 44, Folder 84)
  - Green Ban Movement, Friends of - 1975 (Box 44, Folder 85)
  - Information Applications (Box 44, Folder 86)
  - Institute for Advanced Environment Studies (Box 44, Folder 87)
  - Institute for Higher Studies (Box 44, Folder 88)
  - ILASA - International Inst. Applied Systems Analysis, 1979 (Box 44, Folder 89)
  - Inter- American Institute of Ecology (Box 44, Folder 90)
  - Institute for Higher Studies (Box 48, Folder 1)
  - Editorial Board: International Journal of Environmental Studies (Box 48, Folder 2)
  - ISA: International Studies Association (Box 48, Folder 3)
  - National Organization for Non-Parents (Box 48, Folder 4)
  - Pacific Coast Entomological Society (Box 48, Folder 5)
  - Scientific Aid to Indochina; Task Force of Scientists' Institute for Public Information, 1974 (Box 48, Folder 6)
  - Sierra Club-Scientific Advisory Committee (Box 48, Folder 7)
  - Research Stations (Box 48)
  - Caribbean Research Institute (Box 48, Folder 8)
  - Expense Reports - Chiapas, Mexico 1973 (Box 48, Folder 9)
  - Chiapas Research Station (Box 48, Folder 10)
  - Gombe research Station (see also Goodall in correspondence) (Box 48, Folder 11)
  - Van den Bosch mss.: "Bug Bomb" (Box 48)
  - Van Moeseke, Paul - 1973 (Box 48, Folder 12)
  - Hopkins Marine Station (Box 48, Folder 13)
  - Misc. Papers: R-T (Box 48)
  - Robert C. North: Proposal for a Pilot Study, A Facility for Studies in Human Survival. (Box 48, Folder 14)
- Grant files, Series 2 (Box 36-39)
- Rocky Mountain Biological Laboratory, Series 3
  - 50th Anniversary (1978) (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Administration (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Audit of RMBL (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Board of Trustees (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Bureau of Land Management (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - By-laws (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Cabin (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Constitution (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Correspondence - 1968 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Correspondence - 1969 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Correspondence - 1970 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - Correspondence - 1971 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Correspondence - 1976 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - Correspondence - Disputed Facilities Charges (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - Correspondence - General, 1960-67 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - Correspondence - Incoming, 1974-78 (Box 1, Folder 16-17)
  - Correspondence - Incoming Board of Trustees, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Correspondence - Outgoing, 1972-88 (Box 2, Folder 2-3)
  - Development Brochure (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Draft Environmental Statement, East River and Upper Crystal River Land Use Plan, 1976 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Draft Environmental Statement, East River and Upper Crystal River Land Use Plan, 1978 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Dues (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Elections (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Facility Support Proposal 1979 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Forms - Student Admission (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Forms - Student Evaluation (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Gunnison County Electric Assoc. (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Keith E. Justice, correspondence, 1967-68 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Legal Actions (Box 2, Folder 14-15)
  - Membership Lists (Box 2, Folder 16)
  - Memorandum of Agreement (Box 2, Folder 17)
  - Minutes, 1961-78 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - Newsletter (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
  - Novitski Law Suit (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - Position of the RMBL in Gunnison County (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - Publications (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Research Code (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Slide Set (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Summer Session Posters (long) (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Treasurers Report, 1976 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - URP [Undergraduate Research Participants] Grant 1962 (Box 3, Folder 12-14)
  - URP Grant 1963 (1 Jan) (Box 3, Folder 15-16)
  - URP Grant 1963 (2 Feb-Mar) (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - URP Grant 1963 (3 Apr-Oct) (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Zero Population Growth, Series 4
  - Board of Directors 1970-1972 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Board of Directors 1974-1977 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Correspondence 1969-1972 (Box 1, Folder 3-9)
  - Correspondence 1971-1979 (Box 2, Folder 1-2)
  - Ecology Media Project 1972 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - Equilibrium Fund 1973-1975 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - Field Representatives (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Financial Statements 1970-1971 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Financial Statements 1972-1976 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Frederick Keppel, Consultant 1969 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - General Papers 1969 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - General Papers 1971-1973 (Box 2, Folder 10-12)
  - General Papers 1974 (Box 3, Folder 1-2)
  - General Papers 1975 (Box 3, Folder 3-4)
  - General Papers 1976-1977 (Box 3, Folder 5-6)
  - Harold Seielstad, ZPG Executive Director 1972 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - Johnson Montgomery, ZPG Attorney 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - Larry Barnett, ZPG Fund Trustee 1969-1972 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - Management 1970-1971 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - Membership 1969 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - Myrtel Ashmole, ZPG Director 1969-1970 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - News Releases 1978 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - Newsletter 1969-1970 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Political 1970-1971 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Publications (Box 4, Folder 3-4)
  - Ray Morgan, ZPG Executive Director 1977-1979 (Box 4, Folder 5-6)
  - Richard Bowers, ZPG Executive Director 1968-1971 (Box 4, Folder 7-9)
  - Shirley Radl, ZPG Executive Director 1969-1971 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - ZPG Fund 1971-1974 (Box 5, Folder 1-5)
- Public Appearances, Series 5
  - Libraire Favard, Paris, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Dinah Shore Show, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Future of Man Seminar, Stanford, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Balantine Promotional visit to London, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Common Cause Board Meeting, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - David Frost Show, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - PICA Conference, San Francisco, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - ACLU Dinner, Los Angeles, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - George McGovern, presidential candidate, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Commonwealth Club, San Francisco, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - "AM" show, KGO-TV San Francisco, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 11)
  - American Physical Society meeting, San Francisco, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 12)
  - Ecology and Third World Development, Berkeley, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 13)
  - NBC documentary, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 14)
  - University of San Diego, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 15)
  - University of San Francisco, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 16)
  - University of Santa Clara, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 17)
  - Chuck Cook, CJOR 60 radion, Vancouver, BC Canada, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 18)
  - KCBS radio, San Francisco, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 19)
  - James Wilhite film, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 20)
  - Earth Week, Santa Clara, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 21)
  - Zero Population Growth, San Francisco, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 22)
  - Senator McClosky, San Jose State, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 23)
  - Population Council Seminar, New York, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 24)
  - Interview for the Ecologist magazine, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 25)
  - Kenzo Miyashita, NHK TV interview, Japan, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 26)
  - Rhoda Freier, California Assembly Candidate, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 27)
  - BBC Interview, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 28)
  - Emory University, Atlanta, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 29)
  - University of Georgia, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 30)
  - Harvard University, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 31)
  - Edwin Newman, WNBC TV, New York, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 32)
  - Virgin Islands, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 33)
  - Libraire Favard, Paris, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 34)
  - United Nations Conference on the Human Environment, Stockholm, Folder 1 of 2, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 35)
  - United Nations Conference on the Human Environment, Stockholm, Folder 2 of 2, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 36)
  - Tanzania, 1972 (Box 1, Folder 37)
  - Gombe, Tanzania (cancelled), 1972 (Box 1, Folder 38)
  - "Call Out" show, KGO radio, San Francisco, 1973 (Box 1, Folder 39)
  - Assn. For Medical Studies, Athens, Greece (cancelled), 1973 (Box 1, Folder 40)
  - Mercer University, Macon, Georgia, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 41)
  - Butte College, Durham, California, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 42)
  - Grossmont College, El Cajon, California, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 43)
  - Speeches in Utah, Louisiana, and Florida, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 44)
  - Assn. Of College Stores, San Francisco, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 45)
  - New Zealand and Hong Kong, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 46)
  - Associated Press Managing Editors, Long Beach, California, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 47)
  - Whittier College, Whittier, California, 1974 (Box 1, Folder 48)
  - The Donahue Show, Chicago, Illinois, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 49)
  - UC San Diego, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 50)
  - The Population Institute, Los Angeles, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 51)
  - KOCE TV, Huntington Beach, California, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 52)
  - Georgia Southern College, Statesboro, Georgia, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 53)
  - Mills College, Oakland, California, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 54)
  - Biosytematists, Berkeley, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 55)
  - KPIX TV San Francisco, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 56)
  - Kansas State University, Manhattan, Kansas, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 57)
  - Conference on Cybernetics and Society, San Francisco, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 58)
  - College of Marin, Kentfield, California, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 59)
  - University of Wisconsin Extension, Madison, Wisconsin, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 60)
  - National Center for Atmospheric Research, Boulder, Colorado, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 61)
  - Humanities Project, Bicentennial Committee, Grand Rapids, Michigan, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 62)
  - Cleveland State University, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 63)
  - Mercer University, Macon, Georgia, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 64)
  - Missouri Botanical Garden, St. Louis, Missouri, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 65)
  - Southwest Missouri State University, Springfield, Missouri, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 66)
  - Special Commission on Intenal Pollution, London, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 67)
  - Project Survival videotaping, 1975 (Box 1, Folder 68)
  - The Population Institute, Los Angeles, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 69)
  - University of Ottawa, Ottawa, Canada, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 70)
  - Eastern Illinois University, 1976 (Box 1, Folder 71)